thespecific.com 2018-06-09

# Privacy Policy - The Specific

The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to set forth the practices The Specific follows to respect the privacy of all visitors to this site.

By using this website, you agree to the terms of The Specific Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with all the terms, please do not use our website. The Specific reserves the right to change, add, delete, or alter this Privacy Policy at any time. Your continued use of this website following the posting of any changes to the Privacy Policy will mean that you accept those changes.

The information that we may gather from or about you can fall into two categories; Personally Identifiable Information (“PII”) and Aggregate Information.

### Personally Identifiable Information

We may request and collect personally identifiable information that you voluntarily choose to disclose to us. Examples of personally identifiable information include your name, physical address, e-mail address, telephone number, or any other information that can be used to uniquely identify you.

**The Specific may collect and use Personally Identifiable Information in one or more of the following ways:**

  * To contact you by phone or other means regarding your account, including communication regarding any changes to our policies or account management procedures, information on new product updates, special offers on The Specific services or programs that may interest you, and to process customer service functions
  * To email you information about how to use The Specific services and to inform you of new services, updates or special offers
  * To publish blog comments and enable forum participation
  * Make available to its trusted affiliates, independent contractors, and business partners who will use the information for the purposes outlined herein as necessary to provide the services and for the specific purposes for which the information was collected
  * At the request of law enforcement or governmental agencies or in response to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process, to establish, protect or exercise The Specific’s legal or other rights, to defend against a legal claim or as otherwise allowed by law
  * To protect the rights, property, or safety of The Specific, its employees, patients, or any other person

### Aggregate Information

We may request additional information about you that may or may not be traced specifically back to you. Examples of aggregate information include how many times our site is visited, geographic location, age, or gender.

**The Specific may collect and use Aggregate Information in one or more of the following ways:**

  * To enable us to generate data about the site traffic
  * To make improvements to the website and services
  * To collect demographic characteristics of our target market
  * Such as to customize user experience such as by showing you advertisements that are most relevant to your demographic characteristics, recommending products that may interest you, etc.
  * To share certain demographic and profile data with our agents, contractors, or affiliates

### Security

We take precautions to protect your information. Personal information is stored in a secured manner and always sent via a secure internet channel. When you enter sensitive information, The Specific uses secure socket layer technology (SSL) to encrypt the transmission of that information. However, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable, and The Specific cannot guarantee that the information submitted to, maintained on, or transmitted from its systems will be completely secure. The Specific is not responsible for the circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the site by any users or third parties.

### IP Addresses

The Specific maintains internal logs for Internal Protocol (IP) addresses. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer each time you access the Internet. Your IP address does not contain PII. The Specific collects IP addresses in order to conduct system administration, report aggregate information, conduct site analysis, and to detect improper use of the site.

### Third Party Disclosure

We do not disclose information about you to nonaffiliated third parties, except as permitted by law. For example, we are permitted by law to share information about you to agents, contractors, or affiliates of ours, who help us operate the website, conduct our business, or help us complete a service you requested. All such partners are bound to keep your information confidential. In certain circumstances, we may share information about you if we believe in good faith, that state or federal law requires us to do so, such as to comply with an inquiry from law enforcement officials, when ordered by a court, or by other compulsory legal process. We may also share your information to investigate or prevent suspected illegal activities such as fraud.

### Links to other Websites

Our website may contain links to non-The Specific websites. Links to other websites are provided to you for information and convenience only, and does not constitute an endorsement or recommendation by The Specific. The external sites are not under the control of The Specific and we cannot guarantee the privacy or safety of information you provide to those sites. To ensure protection of your privacy, we encourage you to review the privacy policies of any websites you visit.

### Cookies

We use “cookies” to collect information on how our website is used. Cookies are pieces of information that are transferred to your browser or local device for record keeping purposes. These cookies are not required for site functionality.  Additionally, third-party widgets such as YouTube or Facebook may install cookies depending on their configuration.  You are not required to accept any cookies to use this site.

### Google Analytics

We use a tool called “Google Analytics” to collect information about use of this site. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit this site, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other sites they used prior to coming to this site. We use the information we get from Google Analytics only to improve this site. Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit this site, rather than your name or other identifying information. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. Although Google Analytics plants a permanent cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit this site, the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this site is restricted by the [Google Analytics Terms of Use](http://www.google.com/analytics/tos.html) and the [Google Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html). You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to this site by [disabling cookies](http://www.usa.gov/optout_instructions.shtml) on your browser.

### E-mails

The Specific uses e-mail forms to allow our customers to ask questions about our services or programs. While we make every attempt to protect the personal information that you share with us, it is important to note that an e-mail message is unsecured. Should you choose to send your information via e-mail, you do so at your own risk. We recommend that if your communication is extremely sensitive, you may want to send it by postal mail.

If you choose to correspond to us via e-mail, we reserve the right to retain the content of your email messages as well as your e-mail address or other PII, and our responses.

### Personal Information Provided as Part of User Content

If you include PII as part of any content that you provide to The Specific via public postings to the site, including any bulletin boards, forum posts, etc., such information may be made available to any parties using the site. The Specific does not edit or otherwise remove such information from content uploaded to any bulletin boards, forum posts, etc. before it is posted on the site. If you do not wish to have your personally identifiable information made available in this manner, you must remove any such information from the content before posting. Your contact information (which may include, without limitation, a username and email address) may be included with any content that you post via the site. The Specific is not liable for any damages caused or incurred due to personally identifiable information made available in the foregoing manner.

### Forums

We may provide online forums for users who visit our site. However, any postings will not be protected or confidential.

### Surveys

We may, from time to time, survey visitors on our site. The information collected from these surveys is used in aggregate form to help us improve our site.

### Governing Law

This policy and use of The Specific’s site or services shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of California. If any provision of this agreement shall be unlawful, void, or for any reason unenforceable, then that provision shall be deemed severable from the other provisions and shall not affect the validity of the other provisions.

### WEBSITE ACCESSIBILITY

We are working to improve the accessibility of content on our website. If you have difficulty reading or understanding the content, please call our office and we will assist you. At this time, you may not be able to fill out online forms without assistance. We have paper forms which we can mail to you, or they can be filled out in our office prior to your appointment.

Below, you’ll find a few recommendations to help make your browsing experience more accessible:

### If you have trouble seeing web pages, the [US Social Security Administration offers these tips](https://www.ssa.gov/accessibility/) for optimizing your computer and browser to improve your online experience.

  * [Make your mouse pointer more visible](https://www.ssa.gov/accessibility/mousepointer.html) (Windows only)

If you are looking for **mouse and keyboard alternatives** , speech recognition software may help you navigate web pages and online services. This software allows the user to move focus around a web page or application screen through voice controls.

### If you are deaf or hard of hearing, there are several accessibility features available to you.

### Volume Controls

Your computer, tablet, or mobile device has volume control features. Each video and audio service has its own additional volume controls. Try adjusting both your device’s volume controls and your media players’ volume controls to optimize your listening experience.

### Closed Captioning

Closed captioning provides a transcript for the audio track of a video presentation that is synchronized with the video and audio tracks. Captions are generally visually displayed over the video, which benefits people who are deaf and hard of hearing, and anyone who cannot hear the audio due to noisy environments. We do not currently have video content on our website. [Learn how to turn captioning on and off in YouTube](https://support.google.com/youtube/answer/100078?hl=en).

### Questions or Comments

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Website, or your interaction with this Website, please contact us at:

**September 21st, 2017  
****The Specific  
****7950 Dublin Blvd. Suite 103B, Dublin, CA 94568**
